https://petcem.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
The following policy outlines how “Hartsdale Pet Cemetery” collects and uses information about visitors to this website, and by using this website you acknowledge that you consent to these practices.
This policy is updated from time to time. The latest version will always be published on this page. The modified terms will become effective at the point that they are published here. We strongly recommend that you review this policy from time to time if you are a frequent user of this site.
This website privacy policy was updated on: 05/03/2018
If you have any questions about this policy, please contact us using the information at the end of this document.
What data we gather
We collect website usage data to better understand how visitors use our website. This may include information about the volume of usage, the types of information sought, and other particulars of how this website is used and accessed. We will use this information for managing the website, examining ways of improving the website or other similar objectives.
We may leverage Google Analytics, or other 3rd party tracking solutions to gather and analyze data related to how visitors find and access our site. This information is used only to manage and improve our site.
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
“Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
If you choose to communicate with us through this website, we may collect personally identifiable information. This could include name, email address, physical address, phone number, etc. We may collect such information to help facilitate communications with you. We will use this information for our own internal records and to contact you in response to a specific inquiry.
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us using the contact information at the end of this document
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
Cookies and how we use them
What is a cookie?
A cookie is a small file placed on your computer’s hard drive. It enables our website to identify your computer as you view different pages on our website.
Cookies allow websites and applications to store your preferences in order to present content, options or functions that are specific to you. They also may allow site administrators to see information like how many people use the website and what pages they tend to visit.
How we use cookies
We may use cookies to:
Analyze our web traffic using an analytics package. Aggregated usage data helps us improve the website structure, design, content and functions as described above.
Identify whether you are signed in to our website. A cookie allows us to check whether you are signed in to the site.
Test content on our website. For example, 50% of our users might see one piece of content, the other 50% a different piece of content.
Store information about your preferences. The website can then present you with information you will find more relevant and interesting.
To recognize when you return to our website. We may show you relevant content, or provide functionality you used previously.
Cookies do not provide us with access to your computer or any information about you, other than that which you choose to share with us.
Controlling cookies
You can use your web browser’s cookie settings to determine how our website uses cookies. If you do not want our website to store cookies on your computer or device, you should set your web browser to refuse cookies. However, please note that doing this may affect how our website functions. Some pages and services may become unavailable to you.
Unless you have changed your browser to refuse cookies, our website may issue cookies when you visit it.
Security
We will always hold your information securely.
We have implemented strong physical and electronic security safeguards to prevent unauthorized disclosure or access to any information collected through our website.
Links from our website
Our website may contain links to other websites. Please note that we have no control of websites outside of our domain. If you provide information to a website to which we link, we are not responsible for its protection or privacy.
Contact us
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please
contact us as soon as possible.
x
Online Payment Form
Step 1 of 2
50%
Please complete the form below to make online payments. It’s convenient, secure and user-friendly.
*Fields with red asterisk indicate a required entry.Payment Type*Annual General Care / Flower CareSpecial Day Floral Decoration (check appropriate box below)Payment Plan - Plot Purchase / BurialMonument – Making a deposit to place orderMonument – Paying a balance dueMonument CleaningDonation to Heritage FundOther - please describe what payment is for in Special Instructions belowSprical Day Floral Decorations (Sales Tax Included in Prices Below)
Spring Daffodils: $34.68
Memorial Day - Red, white and blue potted petunias: $34.68
Pet Memorial Day Mums: $34.68
Winter Holiday – Wreath: $45.52
Winter Holiday – Blanket: $59.61
Monument Cleaning
Monument Cleaning $59.61 (tax included)
Plot Number that appears on statement/invoice*Name that appears on statement/invoice*
First
Last
Amount*
Email*
Special InstructionsWould you like to be added to our E-Alerts distribution list?
Yes, I would like to recieve E-Alerts
The Hartsdale Heritage Fund
I would like to add a donation to the Hartsdale Heritage Fund to my checkout.
Donation Options*Supporter up to $99Sponsor $100-499Sustaining member $500-999Angel $1,000-4,999Guardian Angel $5,000-9,999Dr. Samuel K. Johnson Circle of Friends $10,000+Donation: Supporter - up to $99.00*
Donation: Sponsor - $100 - $499*
Donation: Sustaining Member- $500 - $999*
Donation: Angel- $1,000 - $4,999*
Donation: Guardian Angel- $5,000 - $9,999*
Donation: Dr. Samuel K. Johnson Circle of Friends $10,000+*
Enter your payment details below.Billing Address
Street Address
Address Line 2
City
State / Province / Region
ZIP / Postal Code
AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d'IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatini (Swaziland)EthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaRéunionSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUS Minor Outlying IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands
Country
Payment MethodCredit CardCredit Card
American ExpressDiscoverMasterCardVisa
Card Number
Month010203040506070809101112
Year20202021202220232024202520262027202820292030203120322033203420352036203720382039
Expiration Date
Security Code
Cardholder Name
Total
$0.00
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. By closing this banner, scrolling this page, clicking a link, or continuing to browse this site, you agree to this use.OkPrivacy policy
